(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-10-08T22:52:36.149910",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
今日も大天才っ！大天才っ！
Genius again today! Pure genius!
あ〜ずっともっと推し事させてっね！
Ah, let me support you forever and ever!
今日は莉々華の生誕祭ライブ！見に来てくれてありがとー！
Thanks for coming to Ririka's Birthday Celebration Live today!
たくさんのゲストとコラボ曲いっぱい歌うからね！
I'll be singing tons of collab songs with lots of guests!
盛り上がっていこー！
Let's pump it up!
アクスタ 痛バ ぬい 準備万端！
Acrylic stands, ita-bags, plushies—all ready!
オシャレも気合い入れちゃって
I dressed up with maximum effort!
「誰の為なの〜？」って
If you ask, "Who is it for?"
紛うことなき推しの為です！
There is absolutely no doubt—it's all for my fave!
古参 新参も人権は平等
Veterans and newcomers alike enjoy equal rights,
内に秘めた古参マウント
despite the inner urge to flex veteran status!
Not同担拒否ですが
I don't mind sharing my fave with others,
すごーし嫉妬はするかも...！
but I might get just a tiny bit jealous...!
いいね！ボタン足りません...
One "Like" button is just not enough!
これ無料でいいんですか...？
Are you sure this is free to watch...?
好き好きが募る 尊すぎるでしょ...
My love keeps growing, you're just too precious...
困っちゃうなぁ
I'm really at a loss here!
今日も大天才っ！大天才っ！
Genius again today! Pure genius!
他界とか無理絶対考えたくもないなぁ 生き甲斐
Leaving the fandom? Absolutely impossible! I don't even want to think about it! You are my reason for living!
お仕事は年中無休です
My job is 24/7, year-round!
もう大天才 ああ限界
You're such a genius, but I'm at my limit!
これ以上供給されたら困ります
If you give me any more content, I'll be in trouble!
だって召されたいから
After all, I want to be ascended,
冤罪？免罪？あなたが一番です
Even if falsely accused, or exonerated, you're number one!
予約した推しのフィギュア
The figure of my fave that I pre-ordered...
来年発送予定！？
...is scheduled to ship next year?!
（マジ！？）そんなの慣れっこです
(Seriously?!) I'm totally used to that!
忘れた頃にくるけど
It'll arrive when I've completely forgotten about it...
溢れる財源…あ、有限回収ですが！
Overflowing funds... ah, actually, I can only collect a limited amount!
セルカでも많い（マニ） 増えすぎるらびゅー！
Even selfie posts are way too many! Love you!
あ〜もう好き！
Ah, I love you so much!
今日も大天才 大天才
You're a genius again today, a total genius!
しぬ 無理 待って てぇてぇ 考えられないや
I'm dying, it's impossible, wait, so precious, I can't even think!
尊死
Dying from preciousness!
次の現場まで待てないや
I can't wait until the next event!
もう大天才 ああ限界 切り詰めた生活
Such a genius, but at my limit! Living a frugal life...
なにひとつ苦じゃない
...isn't painful at all!
だってこんなにも 幸せ溢れた日々です
Because my days are just so overflowing with happiness!
来年も再来年も
Next year, and the year after next...
その先ずっと何年でも
...and forever for many years to come,
推していたい 好きでいたい
I want to keep supporting you, I want to keep loving you!
demoあなたの幸せがイチバン！
But your happiness is number one!
無理だけはしないでね？
Just please don't overdo it, okay?
あなたとあなたを見つけ出した
To you, and to myself who found you...
私にありがとうを
...I say thank you!
今日も大天才！だーいてんさいっ！
You're a genius again today! A massive genius!
なんでそんなに大天才？困るよ完璧すぎるじゃん
Why are you such a genius? It's not fair, you're way too perfect!
もう大天才！だーいてんさいっ！
Such a genius! A massive genius!
推し無し無理絶対 考えたくもないなあ
Living without my fave is absolutely impossible, I don't even want to think about it!
生きがい！
You're my reason for living!
お仕事は年中無休です
My work is 24/7, year-round!
もう大天才 ああ限界
You're such a genius, but I'm at my limit!
これ以上供給されたら困ります
If you give me any more content, I'll be in trouble!
だって召されたいから
After all, I want to be ascended,
冤罪？免罪？あなたが一番です
Even if falsely accused, or exonerated, you're number one!
推しに勝るものは無し！
Nothing beats my fave!
フーワッ！
Fuu-wa!
フワフワ！
Fuwa-fuwa!
フーワッ！
Fuu-wa!
フワフワ！
Fuwa-fuwa!
我らの星の始まりは (ワパヤ)
The beginning of our star was... (Wapaya!)
触れた瞬間 あらららら (ワパヤ)
...the moment we touched, oh my! (Wapaya!)
お、これは困った
Oh, this is trouble!
二度と元に戻らない大爆発
A big explosion that can never be undone!
ハッ
Ha!
そして星が生まれまして (ワパヤ)
And so a star was born... (Wapaya!)
明け方の１番星は (ワパヤ)
...and the morning star... (Wapaya!)
あなたと出会った これは宇宙を揺るがす大発見
...met with you! This is a universe-shaking discovery!
このままハート打ち上げて どこまでも高くなるの
Let's launch our hearts like this, going higher and higher!
めちゃ飛んじゃいたい！
I really want to fly!
スタースタースタート きっとこのラブは
Star, star, start! This love is surely...
あなたがいなきゃ回らなくて 超新星するぞ？
...unable to spin without you! Let's go supernova!
しちゃうぞ？
We're gonna do it!
あなたに言ってますっ！
We're telling you!
スタースタースタート あの、わかってる？
Star, star, start! Hey, do you know?
ほら目の前にずっとある
Look, it's always right in front of your eyes.
いっせーので見てる
Ready, set, look!
このビッグバン気づいて！
Notice this big bang!
愛は地球くらいに膨らんでこんなになってんぞ
Our love has expanded to the size of Earth, becoming like this!
そうさ大捜索の末は このトキメキのためのアスター
Yes, at the end of our great search is an aster for this heartbeat!
フーワッ！
Fuu-wa!
フワフワ！
Fuwa-fuwa!
フーワッ！
Fuu-wa!
フワフワ！
Fuwa-fuwa!
電波を送信 あなたのハートにノーティス
Transmitting radio waves, sending a notice to your heart!
暇なときでいいよ みたいな顔して めちゃめちゃタイトに
Acting like "whenever you're free is fine," but actually extremely tight!
ちょっと反応くれたら喜ばし
If you give me a little reaction, I'll be so happy!
てかこんなの逃すなんて嘆かわし
I mean, missing out on this would be so deplorable!
我らの星の活動は (ワパヤ)
Our star's activities... (Wapaya!)
割と続いて うむむむ (ワパヤ)
...have been going on for quite a while, hmm... (Wapaya!)
や、これはすごいな
Wow, this is amazing!
つまりあなたと私の創世記
In short, it's our genesis!
このままハート あなたごと連れて
Let's launch our hearts like this, taking you with me...
彼方を目指したの めっちゃ飛んじゃった！
...towards the beyond! I flew so high!
スタースタースタート したこのラブは
Star, star, start! This love we started...
あなたがいなきゃ今頃 調整中だった
...would've still been under adjustment right now if not for you!
してたか？
Was it really?!
ほら今日まで続いた！
Look, it's continued until today!
スタースタースタート ちゃんとわかってね！
Star, star, start! Make sure you understand!
いっそ高度無視して輝く いっせーので
Let's ignore the altitude and shine, ready, set...
あなたと
With you...
わたしで
...and me,
リンクしたいの！
...I want us to link!
ナナナナナナナナ
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na!
愛は地球くらいに膨らんでこんなになってんぞ
My love is expanding to the size of Earth, and it's grown this huge!
ナナナナナナナナ
Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na!
そうだいそうなのはわすれ
Forget about what seems grand,
このときのために スタート！
...start, just for this moment!
リンドン リンドン 心拍数がBPM
Ding dong ding dong, our heart rate matches the BPM!
聴きたいな もっとヒートアップ 感じて
I want to hear it, heat up and feel it even more!
Joy Joy もっと Enjoy リリカルスィーミング
Joy, joy, enjoy even more lyrical swimming!
上々キブンでもっと打っちゃうよホームラン
In high spirits, I'm hitting another home run!
脱帽級の才能 ヒエラルキーワン
Hat-tipping talent, Hierarchy One!
見せてあげるよ ラブリーパーティー
I'll show you a lovely party!
ティルドン ティルドン 巻き起こるコダマ大台風
Tirudon tirudon, brewing up an echoing giant typhoon!
もっとハッピー とことんとことん 届けちゃうよ
Sending you even more happiness to the absolute limit!
そうだろ？こうだろ？ ときめきカロリー
Isn't that right? Like this, right? Heart-throbbing calories!
ラ・ラ・ラヴィッツ いかがですか？
La-la-love-its, how about it?
ちょっとビビッと 感じたら
If you feel a little spark,
止められない 止めどないくらい 胸のドキドキ
...can't stop, unstoppable heartbeat pounding in my chest!
一周回って現在進行形 ぐるぐる追いかけっこ
Spinning around, currently ongoing, a round-and-round game of tag!
あ・ら・ら・ら アラームモード
Oh my, alarm mode!
このまま行くよ！
Let's keep going like this!
リンドン リンドン 心拍数がBPM
Ding dong ding dong, our heart rate matches the BPM!
期待値もヒートアップ もっと感じて
Expectations are heating up, feel it even more!
ジャンピン ジャンピン ディスプレイをジャンプ
Jumpin' jumpin', jumping through the display!
お散歩気分 新世代ライブ
Strolling mood, a new-generation live show!
違法ハローは認めません
Illegal hellos are not allowed!
史上最高の言葉マイスター
The greatest word master in history!
U and I ここからReady
U and I, ready from here!
ずっと見ててね リリカルモンスター・シスターズ
Keep watching us, Lyrical Monster Sisters!
リンドン！
Ding-dong!
マッスル カモン 勢いブンブン
Muscle, come on! Kicking into high gear, vroom vroom!
もっと騒げ Put your hands ブンブン
Make more noise, put your hands up, boom boom!
ドンだけじゃない もっと呑気
Not just boom, let's be more carefree!
跳ねて 伸びて いっちゃって
Bounce, stretch, and let's go!
アゲアゲ アゲアゲ テンパれば 脳内台風
Pump it up, pump it up, if we panic, it's a typhoon in our brains!
やっぱクレイジー ピチピチでいっちゃうよ
After all, it's crazy, let's go in our youthfulness!
キミの愛 キミの愛 ギブ＆テイクガール
Your love, your love, give & take girl!
おかわり いかがですか？
Would you like a refill?
もっとビビッと 感じてよ
Feel the spark even more!
止められない 目が離せない 君のハッシュタグハック
Can't stop, can't take my eyes off your hashtag hack!
もっかい回って通常運転 のびのびいつも通り保存
Spinning once more, back to normal operation, carefree as always!
あ・ら・ら・ら アラカルト
Oh my, à la carte!
そのまま行くよ！
Let's keep going like this!
リンドン リンドン 予測は不可能な
Ding dong ding dong, unpredictable...
想像以上の招待するから
...inviting you to something beyond imagination!
バンピ バンピ キスしたのパニック
Bumpin' bumpin', panicked over a kiss!
突拍子もない発見も通おう
Let's connect even through wild discoveries!
凡庸な日々じゃありません
These are not mundane days!
前代未聞の言葉事典
Unprecedented dictionary of words!
Yes oh yes なんでもオーライ
Yes oh yes, everything is alright!
一緒に信じて リリカルモンスター・メッセージ
Believe in it together, Lyrical Monster Message!
本当はね、りりかちゃんと二人で歌って踊ってみたいって思ってたんだけどね
To be honest, I've always wanted to sing and dance with Ririka-chan...
まさかこんな形で叶うなんて！
I never imagined it would come true like this!
誰が一番驚いてるって、団長だからね！
The one who is most surprised is this Danchou!
感動だよね！
It's so emotional!
テンポが違うときもあるよ
Sometimes our tempos are different,
そこが良いところ
...but that's the best part!
どんな日も笑顔にする
Making you smile on any day,
たくさんたくさん笑わせちゃう
...making you laugh so much,
相乗効果ニコニコ
...synergistic effect, smiling widely!
100万点 あ・ら・ら・ら ラブ＆ピース
1,000,000 points, oh my, Love & Peace!
このまま行くよ！
Let's keep going like this!
まだまだ行くよ！
We're still going!
ついてきてよね！
Keep up with us, okay!
リンドン リンドン みんななら
Ding dong ding dong, if it's everyone,
リンドン リンドン できるはずさ
...ding dong ding dong, you can do it!
リンドン リンドン 聞かせて
Ding dong ding dong, let us hear,
リンドン ドン 大きな声で
...ding dong dong, with a loud voice!
リンドン リンドン 心拍数がBPM
Ding dong ding dong, our heart rate matches the BPM!
期待値もヒートアップ もっと感じて
Expectations are heating up, feel it even more!
ジャンピン ジャンピン ディスプレイをジャンプ
Jumpin' jumpin', jumping through the display!
目指すはただのハピネスサロン
Aiming for nothing but a happiness salon!
違法ハローは認めません
Illegal hellos are not allowed!
史上最高のリリカルの絵だから
Because it's the greatest lyrical picture!
ますますラブ
More and more love!
一緒に信じて リリカルモンスター・メッセージ
Believe in it together, Lyrical Monster Message!
リリカルモンスター・スプリーム イェーイ！
Lyrical Monster Supreme, yay!
リンドン！リンドン！
Ding-dong! Ding-dong!
跪きなさい！
Kneel before me!
汝、この城の扉を叩いた者よ！
Ye who has knocked upon the gates of this castle!
誓いなさい。
Swear it.
このルーナの盾となり 矛となり...
To become Luna's shield and spear...
夜はぐっすり眠れるまで
Until I can sleep soundly at night,
共に歩むことを！
to walk together by my side!
捧げなさい 姫であると
Offer it up, for I am your princess!
ルーナって、紅茶のカップ かちゃかちゃ鳴らさない。えらい！
Luna doesn't clink her teacup. Praiseworthy!
スコーンだって 零さず綺麗に食べて、すごい！
You even eat scones without spilling a crumb. Incredible!
たまにお砂糖 どっちが甘いか間違えちゃうの、かわいい！
Sometimes getting confused about which sugar is sweeter... So cute!
とっておきなのなら（隊長！）
Since you're so special... (Captain!)
ルーナイト 大将！
Roo Knight, General!
誰よりルーナが好きな人？
Who loves Luna more than anyone?
ルーナイト 大将！
Roo Knight, General!
シルクの服持ってきて？
Will you bring me silk clothes?
ルーナイト 大将！
Roo Knight, General!
3時のお茶淹れてくれる人
Who will brew my 3 PM tea?
守れなかったら 即制裁！
If you fail to protect me, instant punishment!
分かってほしいのなら...
If you want me to understand...
これも帝王学を学ぶため。
This too is to study imperial leadership.
愛という名の教育なのなら！
If this is education in the name of love!
守ってルーナイト
Protect me, Roo Knight!
想ってルーナイト
Think of me, Roo Knight!
プロムナードをボイコット なのなのかな
Shall we boycott the promenade?
手の甲にちゅっ
A kiss on the back of my hand,
誓いへのちゅっ
a kiss for our vow.
ガラスの靴 履かせておくれ
Please slide on the glass slipper.
守ってルーナイト
Protect me, Roo Knight!
困ってルーナイト
Worry for me, Roo Knight!
プリンにキャンドル 1粒だけあってもね
Even if there's only one candle on my pudding...
君がいなきゃ だって美味しくない
It won't taste sweet without you here.
誇らしくして
So make me proud,
捧げなさい 姫であると
and offer it up, for I am your princess!
ルーナって、お菓子のあと ちゃんと歯磨きするの、えらい！
Luna brushes her teeth right after eating sweets. Praiseworthy!
目覚ましなくたって、起きられちゃうの、すごい！
Even without an alarm clock, you can wake right up. Incredible!
ステップ こんがらがっちゃったのも、かわいい！
Getting your steps all tangled up... So cute!
今日の褒め言葉はこれなのだから（隊長！）
Since these are today's compliments... (Captain!)
ルーナイト 大将！
Roo Knight, General!
ルーナを本気にさせる人？
Who will make Luna truly serious?
ルーナイト 大将！
Roo Knight, General!
ダイヤの花とか摘んできて？
Pluck some diamond flowers for me? fray?
ルーナイト 大将！
Roo Knight, General!
ドラゴン ペットにできる人？
Who can tame a dragon as a pet?
つべこべ言わずに 即実行！
Don't make excuses, just do it now!
きっと 分かってくれるのなら
If you will surely understand...
こうしてルーナが呼んだのなら
now that Luna has summoned you here...
恋はいつだって 試練なのら！
Love is always a trial!
守ってルーナイト
Protect me, Roo Knight!
踊ってルーナイト
Dance with me, Roo Knight!
オペラハウス貸し切り なのなのかな保存
Shall we reserve the entire opera house?
首筋にちゅっ
A kiss on the neck,
約束のちゅっ
a kiss of promise.
ドレスの薔薇 咲かせておくれよ
Please make the roses on my dress bloom.
守ってルーナイト
Protect me, Roo Knight!
分かってルーナイト
Understand me, Roo Knight!
バルコニーでもらうミルフィーユ シュガーのせちゃう
Mille-feuille with sugar on top on the balcony!
あの子も綺麗だって そうなの？
So she is beautiful too, is that so?
そんな戯言は
Such nonsense...
お止めなさい 姫であると
desist at once, for I am your princess!
守ってルーナイト
Protect me, Roo Knight!
想ってルーナイト
Think of me, Roo Knight!
プロムナードをボイコット なのなのかな
Shall we boycott the promenade?
永遠のちゅっ
An eternal kiss,
この指にちゅっ
a kiss on this finger.
ガラスの靴 履かせておくれ
Please slide on the glass slipper.
守ってルーナイト
Protect me, Roo Knight!
困ってルーナイト
Worry for me, Roo Knight!
プリンにキャンドル 1粒だけあってもね
Even if there's only one candle on my pudding...
君がいなきゃ だって美味しくない
It won't taste sweet without you here.
誇らしくして
So make me proud,
捧げなさい 姫であると
and offer it up, for I am your princess!
行けー！
Let's go!
何を失い 何を手に入れ 耳も塞いで 本日改定
What was lost? What was gained? Blocking our ears, today's revision!
触る ボリューム バキ 手にする全部 いつでもくれくれ
Touch, volume, click! Give me everything you get, always greedy!
適当に 頑張ろうか（そこ！）
Shall we just take it easy? (Right there!)
そんなのだっていいけどさ
That kind of thing is fine too, but...
必死に 頑張ろうぜ（そう！）
Let's work desperately hard! (Yes!)
それが僕ら仕様な
That's just the way we do things!
加湿器じゃねえんだわ
I'm not a humidifier!
そんで貧乏じゃねえんだわ
And I'm not poor either!
うん！ 万事がバッチリ イケてるに決まってる
Yeah! Everything is bound to turn out perfectly cool!
歩こうぜ 難関突破
Let's walk through and break past every obstacle!
ドロドロ新情報 ちゃんと歓迎して
Properly welcoming the muddy new information!
（ワンダラダー!!）
(Wonder-ladder!!)
突っ込めよ 空想像 ちゃんと今日だして
Plunge right into your fantasies, show them off today!
（ワンダラダー!!）
(Wonder-ladder!!)
そうしよう 僕が言うんだもん
Let's do that, because that's what I say!
本当にするんだもん
Because I really will do it!
現実超えろ未来
Future, surpass reality!
作戦も兵器 スイッチでランチャー
Tactics and weapons, launch with a switch!
(ランチャー)
(Launcher!)
スノードームは特者生存ワンダランダー
In this snow dome, it's the survival of the fittest, Wonder Lander!
(ワンダランダー)
(Wonder Lander!)
楽しもう
Let's enjoy this!
面白がれること探して彷徨えば オーバー
Wandering around to find something fun to enjoy... over!
返事聞かせてくれ
Let me hear your reply!
右左なんかじゃない
It's not about left or right.
(カタカタ)
(Clack-clack!)
決めつけて異常設定
Declaring it an abnormal setting!
(カタカタ)
(Clack-clack!)
つまみたくなるなら発射
If you want to grab it, launch!
(発射)
(Launch!)
ライダ ワクワクするぜ発射
Rider, getting excited, launch!
聴いて！推し引き来ちゃ！アイドルオタク楽しい！
Listen! I pulled my fav! Being an idol fan is fun!
でもガチの結婚は立ち直ってません！
But I still haven't recovered from their real-life marriage!
叩け！出るまで回す100%ピックアップ！
Tap it! Keep rolling until you get it! 100% pickup rate!
おっ！
Oh!
天井です！
Pity system reached!
なんだよそれ！そんなこと言っちゃダメだ、おバカ！
What was that? You shouldn't say such things, dummy!
かしこい！ありがとう！
Clever! Thank you!
日々これ最前 全力 Go my way!
Every day, on the front lines! Full power, go my way!
欲したワンダー頂戴だって
Asking to be given the wonder we desire.
息がガガガいいと思う
I think having no breath left is good.
全方位にかっこいいアンテナ張っていなくっちゃ！
We must keep our cool antennas up in all directions!
いつでも心はちゃんと純粋で
Keep our hearts always truly pure.
(ワンダランダー)
(Wonder Lander!)
一等賞の好奇心は絶えず熱心で
Keep our first-class curiosity ever passionate.
(ワンダランダー)
(Wonder Lander!)
一等賞だって
And telling ourselves we are number one...
言い聞かせるの
We gotta tell ourselves that.
調子に乗ったら
Because if we get carried away,
すぐ飽きられちゃうから
we'll immediately be forgotten.
最高なロボットどこですか？
Where is the best robot?
(ワンダランダー)
(Wonder Lander!)
スノードームは特者生存ワンダランダー
In this snow dome, it's the survival of the fittest, Wonder Lander!
(ワンダランダー)
(Wonder Lander!)
新香見つけ
Find a new flavor,
努力とは最後まで諦めないこと
Effort means never giving up until the very end!
メモっておいて
Make sure to write that down!
本当はbaby 自信なんか無いよ
Honestly, baby, I have no confidence...
本当はbaby 不安ばかりで泣きそう
Honestly, baby, I'm so full of anxiety I could cry...
でもねbaby くじけないって決めたの
But you see, baby, I decided I wouldn't give up!
だからbaby 挑戦したいよ未開の
So baby, I want to challenge the unexplored...
地平で
Horizons!
自分だけのフィールドで！
On a field that's mine alone!
ギター！
Guitar!
精神状態 ちゃんと管理して
Manage your mental state properly.
(ワンダランダー)
(Wonder Lander!)
怠慢いく空想 ちゃんと共有して
Share those lazy fantasies properly.
(ワンダランダー)
(Wonder Lander!)
興奮しよう
Let's get excited!
僕が言うんだもん
Because I'm the one saying it!
本当にするんだもん
Because I really will do it!
現実超えろ未来
Let the future surpass reality!
作戦も兵器 スイッチでランチャー
Tactics and weapons, launch with a switch!
(ランチャー)
(Launcher!)
スノードームは特者生存ワンダランダー
In this snow dome, it's the survival of the fittest, Wonder Lander!
(ワンダランダー)
(Wonder Lander!)
楽しもう
Let's enjoy this!
面白がれること探し放題ですから
Since you can search for fun things as much as you want...
無限のフィールドで
On this infinite field!
パニックしちゃってもいいから
It's fine if you panic,
どんなこと言っちゃって
no matter what you might say!
ちなみにこれが僕の答えなんだ
By the way, this is my answer!
胸を張れ
Stand tall!
今を生きるその意味を
Stand tall, the meaning of living in the present...
明くる日も 明くる日も 確かめ進め！
Day after day, verify it and move forward!
イェーイ！かなた先輩ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you so much, Kanata-senpai!
イェーイ！お疲れ様でしたー！
Yay! Great job!
はい！というわけで、みなさん！一条莉々華生誕祭ライブ2025にお越しくださりありがとうございます！
Alright! So, everyone! Thank you so much for coming to the Ichijo Rika Birthday Live 2025!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
イェーイ、イェーイ！今日なんと、もう一人ね、お祝いに、MCに来てくれてる先輩を呼びたいと思います！こより先輩ー！
Yay, yay! Today, we actually have one more guest! I'd like to call out the senpai who came to help host as our MC! Koyori-senpai!
はーい！莉々華ちゃん、お誕生日おめでとうー！
Hi there! Rika-chan, happy birthday!
よーしよしよしよし、莉々華ちゃん真ん中に！
There, there, there. Rika-chan, go in the middle!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
やったー！めっちゃ嬉しいです！来てくれてありがとうございます！
Yay! I'm so happy! Thank you for coming!
ちょっと自己紹介させていただいてもよろしいでしょうか？
Would it be alright if we introduced ourselves?
ありがとうございます！本日の主役！カワイイ・ポジティブ・ジーニアスの一条莉々華だよ！イェーイ！
Thank you! Today's birthday girl, the cute, positive genius, Ichijo Rika! Yay!
大人になりました、莉々華。
Rika has become an adult.
おお、なんかセクシーさに磨きがかかったんじゃないの？
Oh? Haven't you polished your sexiness?
むちむちです、むちむち。
Curvy, so curvy.
いやいやいや！そんなことないです！
No, no, no! That's not true!
じゃ、先輩たちも自己紹介お願いします！
Alright, senpais, please introduce yourselves too!
はい！はーい、こんかなたー！キャッチコピーは握力50キロ！キュッキュッ！握り潰しちゃうぞ！ホロライブ4期生、かなたんこと天音かなたです！
Hello, Kon-Kanata! My catchphrase is 50kg grip strength! Squeeze, squeeze! I'll crush you! Hololive 4th gen, Kanatan, also known as Amane Kanata!
かわいい！イェーイ！
So cute! Yay!
はーい、みんな、こんこよー！ホロライブの頭脳です！ジーニアスこと、博衣こよりだよー！
Alright, hello everyone, Kon-Koyo! I am the brain of Hololive! The genius, Hakui Koyori here!
ああっ！私のジーニアスが、奪われる！
Ah! My "genius" title is being stolen!
誕生日なのに奪っちゃった、ごめん！
I stole it even though it's your birthday, sorry!
本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
なんか変な動きしてました？
Was I making some weird movements?
なんか面白かったから、これやって！
It was really funny, do this!
は！は！
Ha! Ha!
両方にいるからね！両方にいるから！
Because you're on both sides! On both sides!
ありがとう！ありがとう、リリカ！
Thank you! Thank you, Ririka!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
さっそくライブスタートしたわけなんですけど
We've just started our live performance,
はい！
Yes!
今回の配信のハッシュタグ！
but the hashtag for today's stream is
右上のこちら！
right here in the upper right!
こちら！
Right here!
ハッシュタグ #一条莉々華生誕祭2025 となってまーす！
The hashtag is #一条莉々華生誕祭2025!
Xでたくさんたくさんポストしてくれると嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy if you posted a lot on X!
よろしくお願いします！
We'd really appreciate it!
スクショとか、感想とか、もりもり待ってます！
We're looking forward to your screenshots and thoughts!
もりもり待ってるからね！
We're waiting for tons of them!
ということでね、まず、かなた先輩と
And so, first, Kanata-senpai and I
「弱者生存ワンダーランド」歌わせていただきました！ありがとうございました！
sang "Weakness Survival Wonderland"! Thank you so much!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
でも、この曲、本当に可愛くて！
But this song is seriously so cute!
もう踊りもめっちゃね、可愛いし
Even the choreography is incredibly cute!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
こうやってね、ありがとう！
Doing it like this... thank you!
ねー、もうめちゃくちゃ、歌って踊れて、嬉しかったでーす！
Yeah, I was so happy to be able to sing and dance with you!
こちらこそ、リリカの声で聞けて、踊れて、本当に幸せでした！ありがとう！
Same here, I was so happy to hear your voice and dance with you! Thank you!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
そして、このあとね、こよりちゃん先輩とは
And next up, with Koyori-chan senpai,
あの曲を、あの曲を！歌わせていただきます！
we're going to sing *that* song!
一ったい何の曲なんだろう！何だ何だ！
I wonder what song it could be! What is it, what is it?!
もう、リリカの大好きな曲で！
It's a song that I absolutely love!
本当に？あれ？なんかちょっとおかしいぞ？
Really? Wait, something's a bit strange...
何だこれ？なんか赤いよ！赤くなってる！
What is this? It's red! It's turning red!
え？これ大丈夫？なんか出てくる！
Huh? Is this okay? Something is coming out!
うわ、ちょっと！え？嘘でしょ？何これ！何だこれ！何これ！
Whoa, wait! What? No way! What is this?!
近寄らないで！来ないで！
Don't come near me! Go away!
え？え？リリカ！リリカ！リリカ！
What? Ririka! Ririka! Ririka!
あっち行って！来ないで！来ないで！
Go away! Stay back! Stay back!
キャーー！
Kyaaaa!
何これ！？
What is this?!
どうなってんの、リリカ！うざい、何今の！
What's going on, Ririka?! Gross, what was that?!
ちょっと待ってください、あそこに、ゾンビ撃退クリームがある！
Wait a minute! Over there, there's a zombie repellent cream!
何それ？取りに行きましょう！
What's that? Let's go get it!
え？ソフトクリームだろ、あれ！
Huh? That's just soft-serve ice cream, isn't it?!
違います！これは、幻のクリームですよ！
No, it isn't! This is the legendary cream!
え？説明役の人、倒しちゃった...
Wait, we defeated the explanation guy...
これをゾンビに当てれば、たぶんゾンビを
If we hit the zombies with this, we can probably...
たぶん？撃滅できるはず！できなかったらどうすんの！
"Probably"?! ...destroy them! What if we can't?!
いくよ、いくよ！
Here we go, here we go!
リリカ、見せろ、リリカ！えい！
Show them, Ririka! Take this!
あ、物理なんだ！あ、当たった！当たった！
Ah, it's a physical attack! Oh, it hit! It hit!
ちょっと、これ！逃げて！
Hey, wait! Run!
キャー！当たったー！
Kyaaa! It hit!
リリカー！
Ririka!
なんとかなりました！
We managed somehow!
危ない、危ない！
That was close!
なんか一瞬、乗っ取りが起きてたけどな...
For a second there, it felt like a takeover...
乗っ取りは完了ということで！よかったー！
The takeover is complete! Thank goodness!
え、乗っ取られてるの？大丈夫？大丈夫です！
Wait, are you possessed? Are you okay? I'm fine!
あ、戻った！帰ってきた帰ってきた！よかったー！
Ah, she's back! She came back! Thank goodness!
よかったー！
Thank goodness!
何だったんだ、このわけのわからなかったのは...
What was all that nonsense about anyway?
一体何だったんだよ、リリカ！
What in the world was that, Ririka?!
いや、実はですね、ちょっとお化け屋敷感みたいなのを
Well, actually, since we're at an amusement park,
せっかく遊園地だから、味わってほしいなーって思って
I wanted everyone to get a bit of a haunted house feel!
えええ！？ちょっと待って！
What?! Wait a minute!
ジェットコースターがよかった！お化け屋敷なー
I would've preferred a roller coaster! A haunted house, really?
いや、でも、スモークは焚いてほしいって言ったんですけど
Well, I did ask them to bring in some smoke,
まさかゾンビまで出てくるとは思わなくて
but I never expected actual zombies to show up!
多すぎるだろ！あんたの説明と調合のやつ、おかしかったぞ！
There were way too many! Your explanations were all over the place!
物理で解決だったよね、ゾンビ
You ended up taking the zombies down physically!
やばい、やばい
This is crazy!
あ、ということでですね、このあとは、こよりちゃん先輩と
Ah, and so, up next with Koyori-chan senpai...
歌わせて！この状態で歌うの？
We're going to sing! We're singing after *this*?
どういう心境で歌えばいいんだ...
What kind of mindset am I even supposed to sing in?
一応、お化けは湧きだしましたけどね！
Well, the ghosts did end up showing up!
なので、かなた先輩、このあともちょっとここの遊園地でまったりゆっくりしててくださいな！
So Kanata-senpai, please relax and enjoy the amusement park!
遊園地で楽しんで！ありがとうございます！行ってきます！
Have fun! Thank you so much! I'm off!
まったりね、また後でね！
Relax and enjoy, see you later!
嘘でしょ？ま、ま、ま...
No way... W-W-W...
え、ひとりぼっち？僕ひとりにさせられてんだけど...
Wait, I'm all alone? You're leaving me all by myself...
もうキミのココロ ジャックしちゃえ
I'll just hijack your heart already!
こより先輩、来てくれてありがとうございます！
Koyori-senpai, thank you so much for coming!
こちらこそ！WAO!!歌おう！イェーイ！
My pleasure! Let's sing "WAO!!" Yay!
絶対無理！って思っちゃうし だって だって 不安になるし
I keep thinking, "There's absolutely no way!" Because, because, I get so anxious...
全然嘘つけないし だって だって わがまっすぐだし
I can't lie at all! Because, because, I'm stubbornly straightforward!
目指すキラキラの切符はボク次第だ
The ticket to the sparkle I aim for is up to me!
ビターギブアップなんて言わないんだから
I won't say things like "bitter give up"!
じっとしてらんないし だって だって 動いちゃう足
I can't keep still! Because, because, my feet keep moving!
1、2、ステップあっち ちょっぴり進めば 夢の式解けちゃうな
One, two, step over there! If I move forward just a bit, the formula of dreams will be solved!
やりたいボクを キミが好きなボクを ちゃんと余すことなく見せたいな
The "me" who wants to do things, the "me" you love, I want to show you all of it!
あっちゃっちゃ！
Ah-cha-cha!
びっくりするほどできないじゃん
I can't do it at all, it's so surprising!
間違って悩んでばかりじゃん けどキミに
I'm always making mistakes and worrying, but to you...
見つけてほしくて
I want you to find me,
僕は君を迎えに行くんだ
so I'm coming to pick you up.
出会えたならハッピー
If we can meet, we'll be happy!
WAO!! WAO!! 音叫んじゃえ
WAO!! WAO!! Shout out loud!
泣いて泣いて愛してしっぽ振って
Cry, cry, love me, and wag your tail!
WAO!! WAO!! 音叫んじゃえ
WAO!! WAO!! Shout out loud!
だめな僕をどうか覚えておいて
Please remember my clumsy self.
もう君の心チクッとしちゃえ
I'm going to prick your heart!
どうしようかたまに思っちゃって沈んだり
Sometimes I wonder what to do and feel down,
あんがい行けるかもふわり浮かんでまたルンルン
but maybe I can manage, and I float up cheerfully again!
ベッタリがやめられない
I can't stop clinging to you.
「おすわり」ってそれなんだっけ？
What was "sit" again?
うっかりがとめられない
I can't stop being careless.
また歩いて棒に当たるの
I'm walking and running into trouble again.
ワン・ワン・ステップ！死んだフリしてるの？
One-one-step! Are you playing dead?
やめて早くこっちおいで
Stop it, hurry and come over here!
欲しがる君とあげすぎな僕とで
With you wanting, and me giving too much,
もっと行ける気がしています
I feel like we can go even further!
あっ
Ah!
ちょっとびっくりするほどできないじゃん
Wait, I can't do it at all, it's surprising.
間違って悩んでばかりじゃん
I'm always making mistakes and worrying.
だけど君に見つけてほしくて
But still, I want you to find me,
僕は君を迎えに行くんだ
so I'm coming to pick you up.
出会えたならハッピー
If we can meet, we'll be happy!
だって！
Because...
やっぱり一人じゃダメだけど
after all, being alone is no good,
集まってバカしてわおっちゃえば
but if we gather, act silly, and say "WAO!!",
ほらいつでも言える「おかえり！」
look, we can say "Welcome home!" anytime!
僕は君に伝えたいんだ
I want to convey to you,
大いなるハッピー
a grand happiness!
WAO!! WAO!! 音叫んじゃえ
WAO!! WAO!! Shout out loud!
泣いて泣いて愛してしっぽ振って
Cry, cry, love me, and wag your tail!
WAO!! WAO!! 音叫んじゃえ
WAO!! WAO!! Shout out loud!
だめな僕をどうか覚えておいて
Please remember my clumsy self.
目指すキラキラもきっと僕次第だ
The sparkle we aim for is surely up to me!
ヒロイン像なんてもうないんだから
Because there's no fixed image of a heroine anymore!
そうメラメラでブチ切れたりしないで
Yes, so don't burn up and blow your fuse,
はぐれずに希望へ大爆走
and let's sprint towards hope without straying!
君の心チクッとしちゃっていいじゃんハッピーちゃん
It's fine to prick your heart, right, Happy-chan?
常世の闇に 囚われたまま保存
Captured in everlasting darkness,
奏でる悲鳴を
the screams played out...
聞かせて保存
Let me hear them.
FACT / 作詞・作曲・編曲：niki
FACT / Lyrics, Composition & Arrangement: niki
さあ 爪を磨いたら
Now, once you sharpen your claws,
まだ子供のようなあなたのために
for the sake of you, who are still like a child,
ああ 試されたいなら
Ah, if you want to be tested,
その愚かな手に 手錠をかけて保存
put handcuffs on those foolish hands.
常世の闇に 囚われたまま保存
Captured in everlasting darkness,
甘い甘いガムを噛んでた
I was chewing sweet, sweet gum.
いくつもの後悔を
How many regrets...
さあ 捧げて
Now, offer them up.
さり気ない合図に隠れた
Hidden in a casual sign,
答えはすぐに分からせてあげる
I will make you understand the answer soon.
無情な嘘にまみれた
Smeared with heartless lies,
拒んだままに受け止めあげる
I will accept you just as you refuse.
ほら 悲鳴を 聞かせて保存
Come on, let me hear your screams.
さあ 指を鳴らしたら
Now, once you snap your fingers,
この仔猫のような私のために
for the sake of me, who am like this kitten,
ああ 喉が渇いたわ
Ah, my throat has run dry.
薄紅の口に指を散らして
Scattered fingers on pale pink lips...
狭い牢屋に 閉じ込めたまま保存
Locked inside a narrow cage,
首輪に繋がれたいの
I want to be chained to the collar.
くだらないルールじゃ奪えない
Foolish rules can't steal it away.
自由はすでにこの手の中にある
Freedom is already inside these hands.
愛情では測れない
It cannot be measured by love.
弱ったままに選ばせてあげる
I'll let you choose, weak as you are.
ほら 心を開いて保存
Come on, open your heart.
分からないフリをして
Pretending not to understand,
ぼやけてるの
it's all blurry.
もっと熱い暗闇を見せて ねえ ねえ
Show me a hotter darkness, hey, hey.
さり気ない合図に隠れた
Hidden in a casual sign,
答えはすぐに分からせてあげる
I will make you understand the answer soon.
無情な嘘にまみれた
Smeared with heartless lies,
拒んだままに受け止めあげる
I will accept you just as you refuse.
常世の闇に刻むプラトニックを
The platonic bond carved in everlasting darkness,
分からせてあげる
I will make you understand.
ほら 悲鳴を聞かせてよ保存
Come on, let me hear your screams.
夢見ないで保存
Don't dream.
ほら 聞かせて保存
Come on, let me hear them.
[楽曲: オーバード / 作詞・作曲・編曲: 柊キライ]
[Song: Aubade / Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: Hiiragi Kirai]
四六時中 愉快の会で
24/7, at this happy gathering,
面倒くささは 押し付けられてる
they keep dumping all the bothersome chores on me.
何から何まで
Every single thing.
私語はやめて まとめ役なら
Stop chatting! If you're going to be the leader,
聞くを上手に 頷き合ってる
be a good listener, so they say as they nod along.
仲良しこよしで
All playing nice-nice.
さあ だんだんだんだん黙れ 黙り黙りたまえよ
Now, step by step, shut up and hold your tongue.
言えないね そんな強い言葉は
But I can't say such harsh words...
少しだけ 静かにしてほしいな
I just wish they'd be a little quieter...
ああ 私達 大望へ
Ah, toward our grand ambition.
世界征服 征服 やあ やあ やあ
World conquest, conquest! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
果たすその日まで
Until the day we achieve it!
煉獄 煉獄 ええ ええ ええ
Purgatory, purgatory! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
あなたの周りも よ よ よ よ
Everything around you too, yeah, yeah, yeah!
世界征服 征服 あれ あれ あれ
World conquest, conquest! Look, look, look!
約束の地まで
All the way to the promised land!
さあ 掲げよう 罰点 罰点
Now, let's raise the X marks!
てんてん征服 やあやあ
Con-con-conquest! Yeah, yeah!
今日も嫌い そっちのけだね
Hating it today too, but putting it aside.
嫌になるから
Since it's getting annoying,
私一人でも やっておきますね
even if I'm alone, I'll take care of it.
すべて すべて すべて任せて
Leave everything, everything, everything to me.
それをさせてよ
Let me do it.
大事なことなの 分かっているでしょう
It's really important, you understand that, don't you?
四六時中 愉快の会で
24/7, at this happy gathering,
面倒くさいまま 今日も明日も 過ぎていくのでしょう
In this bothersome way, today and tomorrow too will probably pass us by.
花瓶に水をあげましょう
Let's water the vase.
時の中 散ったこと忘れてた
I'd forgotten it withered away with time.
さあ だんだんだんだん黙れ 黙り黙りたまえよ
Now, step by step, shut up and hold your tongue.
言えないね そんな強い言葉は
But I can't say such harsh words...
少しだけ 静かにしてほしいな
I just wish they'd be a little quieter...
ああ 私達 大望へ
Ah, toward our grand ambition.
今と未来 見たかったはずなのに
We were supposed to want to see the present and future, and yet...
世界征服 征服 やあ やあ やあ
World conquest, conquest! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
見えぬその日まで
Until that day yet unseen!
蕩々 蕩々 ええ ええ ええ
Vast and free! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
個人の理 よ よ よ よ
Individual principles, yeah, yeah, yeah!
今は征服 征服 さあ さあ さあ
Now it's conquest, conquest! Come on, come on, come on!
あなたの街中
Throughout your entire city,
形作ろう 罰点 さあ
let's draw the X marks, come on!
世界征服 征服 やあ やあ やあ
World conquest, conquest! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
果たすその日まで
Until the day we achieve it!
煉獄 煉獄 ええ ええ ええ
Purgatory, purgatory! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
あなたの周りも よ よ よ よ
Everything around you too, yeah, yeah, yeah!
世界征服 征服 あれ あれ あれ
World conquest, conquest! Look, look, look!
約束の地まで
All the way to the promised land!
さあ 掲げよう 罰点 罰点
Now, let's raise the X marks!
征服 したら
Once we conquer it,
秘密の部屋をあけましょう
let's open up the secret room!
わー！
Wow!
やったー！
We did it!
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい、ということで、引き続き、ゲストパートをお送りしておりました。が！
Alright, so we've been bringing you our guest segment... But!
なんと！もう一人、MCに呼びたいと思います！
We actually have one more guest to call up for our talk segment!
誰だ誰だ誰だ？
Who is it, who is it, who is it?
トワ先輩！
Towa-senpai!
はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes!
イェーイ！
Yay!
来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming!
いや、こちらこそ！
No, thank you for having me!
ちょっとせっかくなんで、自己紹介していただいてもいいですか？
Since you're here, would you mind introducing yourself?
はーい！
Sure!
オッケー！ホロライブ4期生の、あれ？
Okay! From Hololive 4th Gen... Wait...
あれ？
Huh?
あれ？間違えた？
Wait, did I get it wrong?
常闇トワです！
I'm Tokoyami Towa!
「こんやっぴー」がないから言えないんだ。「こんやっぴー」！
I couldn't say it without "Kon'yappi"! "Kon'yappi"!
こんやっぴー！
Kon'yappi!
どうぞ！
Go ahead!
はい、皆さんまたかねー。ホロックスの女幹部、鷹嶺ルイと申します。
Hi, everyone! Matakane! I'm Takane Lui, the executive officer of holoX.
りりか、お誕生日、おめでとう！
Ririka, happy birthday!
おめでとうございます！
Happy birthday!
めっちゃ嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
喜びの舞！
The dance of joy!
呼んでくれて嬉しいよ、お誕生日にさ。
I'm so glad you invited me on your birthday.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ねー。トワ先輩も、もう本当にりりかに優しくしてくれる、りりか的には姉御的な存在なので。
Towa-senpai is always so kind to me, she's like a big sister figure to me.
えー！慕ってくれて、慕ってくれて！
Aw, thank you for looking up to me!
トワ、全然謙遜しないんだよね。
Towa doesn't show any modesty at all, does she?
ルイも、トワのこと慕ってるよね。
Lui, you look up to Towa too, don't you?
あー、トワ、トワ、トワ。
Ah, Towa, Towa, Towa.
だから、めっちゃ嬉しいです！
So I'm super happy!
イェーイ！
Yay!
やばい、このキラキラについていけない。
Oh no, I can't keep up with this sparkly energy!
キラキラ、キラキラ、キラキラ！
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle!
ちなみにどうですか？
By the way, how is...
私の遊園地なんです！
This is my amusement park!
遊園地！
Amusement park!
めっちゃ遊園地。いい最高！
It's totally an amusement park. This is the best!
いいでしょ、いいでしょ。
Great, isn't it?
ジェットコースターもあるんだよ。
There's also a roller coaster.
乗りたい。後で乗ろうよ。
I want to ride it. Let's ride it later.
色々ある。結構すごいスピードだよ。
There are lots of things. It goes pretty fast!
スピードすごい！
The speed is crazy!
ちゃんと乗れるようになってるんで是非。
You can actually ride it, so please do!
じゃ、後で一緒に乗ろうよ。
Then let's ride it together later.
乗りたい、乗りたい！
I want to ride it, I want to ride it!
でも一旦実は、出店も用意してるので。
But first, I actually prepared some food stalls...
出店？
Food stalls?
そう、こっちに来てください。こっちこっち！
Yes, please come over here. This way!
お、出店。何があるのかな？
Oh, food stalls. What do they have?
何の出店？
What kind of stall is it?
こっちです、こっちこっち。
This way, this way.
はーい。
Okay!
うわ、すごい！
Wow, amazing!
お、出店もありますよ。
Oh, there's even a food stall here!
すごーい！
Amazing!
ぽつんと。
It's standing alone...
ぽつんじゃない。ぽつんじゃないよ。
It's not alone! It's not alone.
バルーンも付いてる。
It has balloons on it too.
そうですよ。
That's right.
ちょっとこの出店でソフトクリーム食べれるんで。
You can get soft-serve ice cream at this stall.
りりかが先輩たちに、
Since you always take care of me,
いつもお世話になってる先輩たちにご馳走します！
I'm going to treat you both!
やったー！
Hooray!
ご馳走ですか？
A treat?
もちろんですよ！
Of course!
さすが所長だよ。
As expected of the president!
食べましょう、食べましょう。
Let's eat, let's eat.
お、近くなりましたね。
Oh, we got closer.
じゃ、いただきます。
Then, thank you for the food.
ありがとう。
Thank you!
うわ、美味そう。
Wow, looks delicious.
やったー！
Yay!
もらいました、もらいました。
We got them, we got them.
よかったら食べてください。
Please help yourselves.
いただきます。
Thank you for the food.
いただきまーす。
Let's eat!
ありがとう、美味いわ。
Thank you, it's delicious.
美味しい。
Delicious!
サンキュー！
Thank you!
甘ーい！
So sweet!
ね、めちゃくちゃ濃厚で美味いな。
Right? It's super rich and delicious.
うん、いいソフトクリーム。
Yeah, a really good soft-serve.
あ、よくアイス食べる？
Ah, do you eat ice cream often?
食べる。
I do.
食べる、アイス大好き。
I eat it, I love ice cream.
大好きですか？よかった！
You love it? I'm so glad!
私、ミルクが好きなの、ミルクが。
I really like milk flavor, the milk.
ミルク美味いよね。
Milk flavor is delicious, isn't it?
ルイ姉は？
What about you, Lui-nee?
私もね、このワッフルコーン大好きで。
Me too, I love waffle cones.
よく食べるよ。
I eat them quite often.
ワッフルコーンいいよね、高級感あるわ。
Waffle cones are great, they feel fancy.
それはそう。
That's very true.
りりかは何がいいの、これの？
What about you, Ririka? What do you like?
りりかは実は、あんまりアイス食べないんですけど...
Actually, Ririka doesn't eat ice cream that much...
食べないんだ。
You don't?
でも、氷が好き。
But, I like shaved ice/ice pops.
氷系ね。
So ice-based ones.
クリーム系だけどね、今日は。
But today, it's cream-based.
しょうがないじゃん！
I couldn't help it!
クリームしか置いてなかったんだもん！
They only had cream-based ones here!
めちゃくちゃ美味いです。ありがとうございます。
But it's super delicious. Thank you very much!
ということで、今回のライブステージも紹介させてください！
So, let us introduce today's live stage as well!
お願いしまーす。
Please do!
じゃじゃーん！今回はなんと遊園地ステージとなっております！
Ta-da! This time, it's an amusement park stage!
すごい！
Amazing!
ロマンチック。
It's romantic.
夜空がすごく綺麗。しかもすごくない？
The night sky is so beautiful. And isn't this great?
あ、ジェットコースターが今登ってる！
Oh, the roller coaster is going up right now!
うおー！すげえ！
Whoa! Awesome!
速い！
It's fast!
マジ速い。
Seriously fast.
結構、時々ね...
Sometimes, on occasion...
シュッシュって通るかもしれない、もしかしたら。
It might zoom past us, maybe.
お、来るの？みたいな。
Like, "Oh, is it coming?"
今？みたいな。
Like, "Right now?"
色々乗れるのもあるんで、よかったら先輩たち、この後もまったりしていってください。
There are other rides too, so seniors, feel free to relax here later.
いいんですか？
Really?
じゃ、二人で乗ってね。
Then, you two go ride it.
乗って。
Go ahead and ride.
ライブ見てるよ、こうやって手振りながら。
We'll watch your live show while waving our hands.
映ったらごめんね。
Sorry if we get caught on screen.
映るかもしれない、どっかに。
You might get caught on screen somewhere.
どっかに映ろう。
Let's get caught somewhere!
ねぇ、本当に今日、お二人に来ていただいて、
Seriously, I'm so incredibly happy
めちゃくちゃめちゃくちゃ嬉しくて。
that both of you could come today.
まず一個目が、りりかね、常闇先輩の「Fact」を一緒に歌わせていただいたんですけど、
First off, I got to sing Tokoyami-senpai's "Fact" with her.
デビューした直後に、ReGLOSSで同時視聴、
Right after our debut, ReGLOSS did a watch-along
常闇先輩のライブを同時視聴させていただいて、
of Tokoyami-senpai's live show.
その時に、この「Fact」聴いて、「やべえ、めちゃくちゃかっけえ！」って。
When I heard "Fact" then, I thought, "Damn, that's so cool!"
「りりかもこんな風に歌えるようになりたい、踊れるようになりたい」って。
"I want to be able to sing and dance like that too!"
そんなに興奮してくれたの？
You were that excited about it?
マジです、これ。
I'm totally serious.
だから今回こうやって一緒に歌って踊ってもらえて本当に嬉しいです。ありがとうございます。
So I'm really happy we could sing and dance together today. Thank you so much!
こちらこそ、本当に一緒にできて嬉しかったよ。ありがとうね。
Likewise, I was really happy to perform together. Thank you too!
ありがとうございました。素敵だった。
Thank you very much. It was wonderful.
ルイ姉とはね、「Overlord」を歌わせていただきましたけど。
And with Lui-nee, we performed "Overlord."
めっちゃ嬉しい。
I'm so happy.
「Overlord」もめちゃくちゃ大好きな曲で。
"Overlord" is a song I really, really love too.
言ってくれてたもんね。
You've mentioned that to me before.
そうなんです。一緒に歌いたいなっていつかって言ってて、
Yes. I'd been saying I wanted to sing it together someday,
今回こうやって夢が叶ってめちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！
so I'm so happy my dream came true today!
嬉しい。めっちゃかっこよかったよ、ダンスも歌も。
I'm glad. It was super cool, both the dance and the vocals.
大人の色気、ちゃんと出せてましたか？
Did I manage to show off some mature sexiness properly?
出せてましたよ、大人の色気。
Yes, you definitely showed off that mature sexiness.
やったー！嬉しい。
Yay! I'm so happy.
素晴らしかったです。
You were wonderful.
大人の色気？
Mature sexiness?
やっぱ大人の色気ね、見せていきましたから。
After all, we showed off our mature sexiness.
いかがだったでしょうか？
How did you like it?
How was it?
なんでちょっと引いてるの？
Why are you backing away?
いや、嬉しい。本当にありがとうございました。
No, I'm just so happy. Thank you so much, really.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you very much!
まだりりか、この後もあるので、
Ririka still has more performances after this,
もしよかったらお二人から「頑張れ」のエールをいただきたいです。緊張をほぐしたい。
so if you don't mind, I'd love a word of encouragement from you both!
いや、ソフトクリームももらったし、お礼のね。
Well, we did get soft-serve ice cream, so as a thank you...
お礼をね、しましょう。
Let's give her our thanks.
お願いします！
Yes, please!
じゃ、せーので行くね。
Then, on three.
せーの。
One, two...
頑張れー！
Do your best!
あれ、りりか？
Huh, Ririka?
りりかどこ行った？
Where did Ririka go?
りりか？
Ririka?
りりかー！
Ririka!
恋々私のわがまま 放っといて
Leave my selfishness alone
止めらんない 熱に任せて
I can't stop, leaving it to the fever
懲り懲りだルールは Break It Down
I'm sick of rules, break it down
我慢できない Let me free
I can't hold back anymore, let me free
目が眩んでしまいそうな出で立ちの
Standing there looking so dazzling...
mermaid 憧れてたけれど
I used to yearn to be a mermaid, but...
だって今は何も響かない
Because nothing resonates with me now.
I know who I am
ブランディングには勘弁
Give me a break with branding,
今は完全無視よ 何であれ
I'm completely ignoring it now, no matter what.
I'm of the greedy style
他人のウワサも 興味ないの
I don't care about others' rumors.
ありのままでいたい
I just want to be myself.
Going on my way もう放っといて
Going on my way, just leave me alone.
止められない熱味任せて
Surrendering to this unstoppable passion.
凝り固まったルールは Break it down
Break down those stiff rules.
我慢できない Let me free
I can't hold back, let me free.
We are special でしょ 揺るがないプライド Blues
We are special, aren't we? An unwavering pride.
それだけでいいの
That's all that matters.
たらればだらけの 退屈な日々を Break it down
Break down those boring days full of "what ifs"...
Break it!
We are special でしょ
We are special, aren't we?
誰に言われても 私は歌うよ
No matter what anyone says, I will sing!
アンフェアばかりの 世界など Break it down
In a world full of unfairness, break it down!
Break it! 進め
Break it! Move forward!
ハイテクなメイクやファッション
High-tech makeup and fashion,
Self-love には敵わないよ
they can't compete with self-love.
体と心 誰のものでもないでしょ
My body and mind don't belong to anyone else, right?
いい加減に大人だよね
It's about time to be an adult, isn't it?
Pura-pura, apa adanya, tidak sempurna tapi sepenuhnya diriku
Pretending, just as I am, imperfect but fully myself.
でも今は楽しいよ
But I'm having fun right now,
ありのままでいられるから
because I can just be myself!
Going on my way もう放っといて
Going on my way, just leave me alone.
止められない熱味任せて
Surrendering to this unstoppable passion.
凝り固まったルールは Break it down
Break down those stiff rules.
我慢できない Let me free
I can't hold back, let me free.
We are special でしょ
We are special, aren't we?
揺るがないプライド
An unwavering pride.
それだけでいいの
That's all that matters.
たらればだらけの 退屈な日々を Break it down
Break down those boring days full of "what ifs"...
Break it!
We are special でしょ
We are special, aren't we?
誰に言われても 私は歌うよ
No matter what anyone says, I will sing!
アンフェアばかりの 世界など Break it down
In a world full of unfairness, break it down!
Break it! 進め
Break it! Move forward!
You can't break me down, break me, yeah
Break it down, break it down
Break it down, break it, susume
Break it down, break it, move forward!
Break it down, break it down
Going on my way もう放っといて
Going on my way, just leave me alone.
止められない熱味任せて
Surrendering to this unstoppable passion.
凝り固まったルールは Break it down
Break down those stiff rules.
我慢できない Let me free
I can't hold back, let me free.
それじゃあいくわよ、SUPER DUPER!
Alright, here we go! SUPER DUPER!
ReGLOSSで、せーの...
With ReGLOSS, one, two...
ReGLOSS!
目くるめく 好奇心は森羅万象
A dazzling curiosity encompassing all of creation,
行く末 神さえも知らぬ場所
heading towards a place unknown even to God.
混ざり気のない 情熱が
Our pure passion...
澄ました 空虚を逆撫でたとこ
rubbed the clear emptiness the wrong way.
熱気に浮かされよう 夜も友に バトンを繋ぐ
Let's be carried away by the heat, befriending the night as we pass the baton.
リズムも目まぐるしい 時代も全部
The rhythm, the dizzying times, everything...
忘却の彼方へ 笑い飛ばそう
Let's laugh them off into oblivion!
Give me, give me the beat right now!
SUPER DUPER オートクチュールなシャングリラ
SUPER DUPER, an haute couture Shangri-La,
日が暮れるまで 踊ろうよ
Let's dance until the sun goes down.
誰が何と言おうと 気にしちゃいない
No matter what anyone says, we don't care.
高い熱量 そうただ楽しむだけ規定変更
High thermal energy, yes, we're just here to have fun.
美しい声を 響かせて
Let our beautiful voices resound!
俯いた世界を 変えて見せてよ
Show us you can change this downcast world!
SUPER DUPER 今後ともよろしく マジステキな逆転
SUPER DUPER, looking forward to working together, a truly wonderful comeback!
とうとう言ってみせる 激アツ劇変
We'll finally show you a super hot, dramatic shift!
転生してももう一度 ここにカムバック
Even if we reincarnate, we'll comeback here again.
人生そのものが センセーショナルな漫画
Our lives themselves are a sensational manga.
ビギナーから一躍 羽ばたいてオリジナル
From beginners, we suddenly soar to become original.
一番めがけて 走り出せ
Aiming for number one, start running!
地に足つけてジーニアス
Keep your feet on the ground, genius!
深まっちゃう夜に 灯すはワンダー
In the deepening night, what we light is wonder.
うつしだしたとて 問題ない
Even if it's exposed, there is no problem.
高鳴る胸の動悸 愛してやまないもの
The throbbing of our racing hearts, things we can't help but love,
疑うことも知らないまま
without ever knowing doubt.
So it's okay 覚悟はできているよ保存版
So it's okay, we are fully prepared.
Give me the, give me the beat right now!
SUPER DUPER オートクチュールなシャングリラ
SUPER DUPER, an haute couture Shangri-La,
日が暮れるまで 踊ろうよ
Let's dance until the sun goes down.
誰が何と言おうと 気にしちゃいない
No matter what anyone says, we don't care.
満たした会場
The filled venue...
そっとただ楽しむだけ
...just quietly enjoying it.
美しい声を響かせて
Making our beautiful voices echo.
Yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, oh oh
俯いた世界を変えてみせよう
Let us change this downcast world!
Yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah...
Super Duper
一喜一憂も
Riding a wave of hope and fear,
一期一会そういうね
a once-in-a-lifetime encounter, that's how it is.
一心同体でいて
Let's remain as one in body and soul.
こよなく愛したメロディと
With the melody I loved so dearly,
会えなくて手放したレプリカ
and the replica I let go of because we couldn't meet.
まもなく君との境界
Soon, the boundary with you...
線を越え Release
...will be crossed, release!
Super Duper 踊る 巡るの シャングリラ
Super Duper, dancing and spinning in Shangri-La,
日が暮れるまで踊ろうよ
let's dance until the sun goes down!
誰が何と言おうと気にしない
No matter what anyone says, we don't care!
満たした会場
The filled venue...
そっとただ楽しむだけ
...just quietly enjoying it.
美しい声を響かせて
Making our beautiful voices echo.
Yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, oh oh
俯いた世界を変えてみせよう
Let us change this downcast world!
Yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah...
Super Duper
というわけで！
And so!
ReGLOSSで、「SUPER DUPER」お送りしました！
ReGLOSS presented "SUPER DUPER"!
みんな来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for coming!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
さっきもやったんだけど、もう一回やってもいい？
We did it earlier, but can we do it one more time?
うん、いいよ！
Yeah, sure!
それじゃあ行きます！リーチザトップ！ウィーアー
Here we go! Reach the top! We are...
ReGLOSS!
せっかくだからちょっとみんなに自己紹介してほしくて、じゃあ、奏から！
Since we're here, let's do self-introductions. Kanade, you start!
はい！
Okay!
えっと、一条莉々華の恋人、音乃瀬奏です！
Um, Ichijou Ririka's lover, Otonose Kanade!
おれ？おれ？いつの間に？恋人だったんだ！
Me? Me? Since when were we lovers?!
莉々華ちゃん大好きだよ！
I love you so much, Ririka-chan!
やったー！
Yay!
そして？
And next?
一条莉々華のペット、火威青です。
Ichijou Ririka's pet, Hiodoshi Ao.
ペット？！ワンワン！
Pet?! Woof woof!
よしよしよしよしよしよしよしよし。
Good boy, good boy...
そして？
And next?
えーっと、一条莉々華の、えーっと、配信デスクの上のタンブラーを置く、あのコースターみたいなやつ、儒烏風亭らでんです。
Uh, the coaster-like thing on Ichijou Ririka's streaming desk where she puts her tumbler, Juufuutei Raden here.
なにそれ？！
What on earth is that?!
物じゃん！
That's just an object!
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
みんな来てくれて本当にありがとうね！
Thank you so much everyone for coming!
楽しかった！
It was so much fun!
誕生日だっけ？大人になったんだっけ？
Is it your birthday? Did you become an adult?
そうです、莉々華、大人になりました！
Yes, Ririka has become an adult!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
誕生日っていいな、毎日誕生日がいい。
Birthdays are great, I wish it were my birthday every day.
毎日年取ることになるけど。
But you'd age a year every day.
じゃあ、この話は終わりということで。
Okay, let's end this conversation then.
はい、じゃあここからはね、ちょっと告知をさせていただきたいなと思っております！
Alright, from here on, we have a few announcements we'd like to share!
告知？！
Announcements?!
もしかして、一条莉々華、誕生日記念2025グッズが出るってこと？！
Could it be... Ichijou Ririka Birthday Celebration 2025 Merchandise is being released?!
じゃあ、こちらをご覧ください！ドン！
Then, please take a look at this! Ta-da!
じゃじゃん！
Tada!
かわいい！
So cute!
俺の莉々華！
My Ririka!
こちらね、初めての生誕祭のグッズということで、盛りだくさんのグッズになっております！
Since this is my first birthday celebration merchandise, we have a huge variety of items!
今回はですね、イラストはトマリ先生に描いていただきました。本当にありがとうございます！
This time, the illustration was drawn by Tomari-sensei. Thank you so much!
可愛くて美しくて最高だよね。
It's cute, beautiful, and absolutely the best.
じゃあ詳細も見ていきたいと思います。まずは、こちら！
Let's look at the details. First up, this!
イェーイ！出た出た。みんな画角に入ってね。
Yay! There it is. Everyone, get in the frame.
まずは、アクリルスマホスタンドです！
First is the Acrylic Smartphone Stand!
今回ね、オリジナル衣装で歌って踊ってる莉々華の描き下ろしイラストを…
It features a newly drawn illustration of Ririka singing and dancing in her original outfit...
はい、してもらいました。もうめちゃくちゃ本当に可愛いし、スマホスタンドなので、スマホを上に置けるということ。
Yes! It's incredibly cute, and since it's a smartphone stand, you can place your phone on it.
つまり、ずっと一緒にいれるということ！
Which means we can be together forever!
イェーイ！
Yay!
大事につかってください。そして、続いてはこちら！
Please use it well. Next is this!
ジョン！かわいい！
Ta-da! So cute!
ランダムラバーストラップ！やっぱり莉々華オタクなので、自分自身も。
Random Rubber Strap! Since I'm an otaku myself,
うーん、何にしようかなって考えたときに、ラバスト欲しすぎ！って思って。
when I was thinking of what to make, I really wanted rubber straps!
今回ね、土倉エク先生に、4種類もの莉々華を書き下ろしていただきました。めっちゃ可愛い！
This time, Dokura Eku-sensei drew four different versions of Ririka for us. They're so cute!
悪役令嬢なの？
Is one a villainess?
そうだよ、悪役令嬢の莉々華もいます。
Yes, there's a villainess Ririka.
莉々様！
Lady Riri!
そう、莉々様。莉々様ですわ！
Yes, Lady Riri. I am Lady Riri!
無理しました、今。
I pushed myself too hard just now.
こちらはえっと、ランダムで1種類封入されております。
And this is randomly enclosed with one type.
おおー！
Ohhh!
そして、続いてはこちら！
And next is this!
ジャン！
Ta-da!
ウニペンケース！
The Uni Pen Case!
え、可愛い！めっちゃ良い！
Eh, so cute! That's so good!
ふわふわでね、もう、めちゃくちゃ可愛い！
It's so fluffy and super cute!
え、お腹裂かれてる？
Eh, is its stomach ripped open?
お腹じゃなくて背中！背中！
Not the stomach, the back! The back!
背中が裂いてますが、まあ内臓がペンみたいな感じでね。
The back is split open, but the inside is like a pen.
なるほど。
I see.
可愛がってあげてください。
Please cherish it.
普段使いできるので、ぜひぜひ使ってください。
Since it can be used daily, please do use it.
可愛い！
Cute!
続いてはこちら！
Next is this!
なんと、限界飯プレートが出ます！
Surprisingly, the Genkai-meshi plate is coming!
可愛い！
Cute!
お米？お米？
Is that rice? Rice?
そう、これね、あのお米が敷いてあるような
Yes, this is a plate with an illustration...
イラストのプレートなので、この上にね、こう具材を乗せれば、
...that looks like rice is spread out, so if you put toppings on it...
簡単にお手軽に限界飯が作れるという優れものになっております。
...you can easily make a Genkai-meshi. It's a great item.
え、めっちゃ良い！
Eh, so good!
ウニも、ウニもちょっと書いてある。
Uni is also written a little bit.
そう、ウニもいますよ。
Yes, Uni is there too.
可愛い！
Cute!
じゃあ続いてはこちら！
Then next is this!
ジョン！
Ta-da!
まあね、ボイスもやろうかなということで、
Well, since we're doing voice packs too...
今回みんな待望のASMRボイス、収録しております！
...this time, we've recorded the long-awaited ASMR voice!
やったー！すごい！
Yay! Amazing!
1個目は、「莉々華の部屋で一緒にゲーム」で、
The first one is "Playing Games Together in Ririka's Room,"
まあ、莉々華のおうちで、隣でなんか
...and it's a lovey-dovey voice pack where...
一緒にゲームをしてるかのような、ラブラブボイスとなっておりますので、よろしくお願いします！
...it feels like you're playing games together next to me, so please look forward to it!
いいねー！買うしかない！
Nice! Have to buy it!
そして、なんとですね、フルセットの購入特典もございます。こちらです。ジャン！
And surprisingly, there's also a full set purchase bonus. Here it is. Ta-da!
はい、まずは、直筆サインがついてきます！
Yes, first of all, it comes with a handwritten signature!
で、こちらはですね、もう莉々華限定とかじゃなくて、
And for this, it's not limited or anything,
買ってくださった方には全員にお付けしたいと思っているので、ぜひいっぱい、いっぱい購入してもらえると嬉しいです。
I want to give it to everyone who purchases, so I'd be really happy if you bought a lot.
ポストカードに、直筆サインをつけてお渡しします。
I will write a handwritten signature on the postcard.
で、もう1つが、さっき「ASMR 1個目は」って言ったんですけど、
And another thing, earlier I said "the first ASMR is...",
2個目がこちらで「あなたのお誕生日をお祝い」ということで、
...but the second one is this, "Celebrating Your Birthday,"
今回ね、まあ今日は莉々華の誕生日をみんなにこうやってお祝いしてもらってるわけですけど、
and although today everyone is celebrating Ririka's birthday like this...
莉々華もみんなの誕生日をお祝いしたいと思って、今回準備しました。ぜひ自分の誕生日に聞いてください！
...Ririka also wanted to celebrate everyone's birthday, so I prepared this. Please listen to it on your birthday!
はい、じゃあ改めて、フルセットはこちらとなります。
Okay, so once again, the full set is this.
じゃん！いや、なんて豪華なんだ。あまりにいっぱいいすぎて、ねえ、もう、絶対に買ってください。絶対に、絶対に。よろしくお願いします。
Ta-da! Wow, how luxurious. There are just so many things, so, really, please buy it. Absolutely. Please.
そして、さらに、えー、タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として、
And further, as a full set bonus for the talent premium goods...
えー、去年から発売されているホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで、なんと使用できるカードが1枚ついてきます！
...we have a card that can actually be used in the Hololive Official Card Game, which is out since last year!
カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入された方のみが対象となります。
The card is only eligible for those who purchased from the Hololive Production Official Shop.
特典につくのは、推しをアピールできるキーカード、推しホロメンのカードです。
The bonus is a key card that allows you to show off your favorite, a card of your favorite Holomem.
カードの詳細や遊び方などについては、ホームページにてご確認ください。
Please check the homepage for card details and how to play.
なんと、実はまだお知らせがあるんです。
Actually, there's still more news!
こちらをご覧ください。デン！
Please look at this. Dun!
お、出た！よしよしよし。
Oh, it's out! All right, all right.
一条莉々華のLINEスタンプの制作が決定しました！
The production of Ichijou Ririka's LINE stamps has been confirmed!
詳細はね、後日公開となりますので、ご確認のほどよろしくお願いします。
The details will be released at a later date, so please check it out then.
めっちゃ可愛くない？ヤバすぎるでしょ、いっぱい使ってください。
Isn't it super cute? It's crazy, right? Please use them a lot.
以上、一条莉々華生誕祭記念ライブのグッズ情報でした！みんな買って頂けると、とっても嬉しいです。
That's all for the merchandise info! I'll be so happy if everyone buys them.
改めてにはなるんですけど、もう本当にこうやってね、今回、ライブ生誕ライブ、無事やることができて、もうめちゃくちゃ嬉しい気持ちでいっぱいです。
Once again, but really, doing this birthday live safely, I'm just filled with so much happiness.
たくさんの応援コメント、もう常日頃からね、莉々華にいっぱい届いております。
So many supportive comments always reach Ririka every single day.
みんなが応援してくれたおかげで、また莉々華、ダンス頑張れた！歌も頑張れた！
Thanks to everyone's support, Ririka could work hard on dancing and singing again!
これからも、たくさん、たくさん、みんなとおろんな景色見れるように頑張りますので、よろしくお願いします！
I will do my best to see many different sights with everyone, so please support me!
でさ、あれ？
And, wait, huh?
皆...
Everyone...
どこ行った？消えた？
Where did they go? Did they disappear?
え？なんで？どこー？
Eh? Why? Where are you?
莉々、こっちだよー！こっちこっち！
Riri, over here! Over here, over here!
ああ、乗ってた！
Ah, you were riding it!
メリーゴーラウンドに乗ってたの！
We were riding the merry-go-round!
楽しそう。
Looks fun.
白馬の王子様みたいになってるじゃん、番長。
You look like a prince on a white horse, Bancho.
そうだろ、そうだろ。
Right, right?
いいなー。莉々華も乗りたい気持ちはもういっぱいあるんだけどさ、
Jealous. Ririka also really wants to ride it, but...
この後まだアンコールライブもあるから。
...we still have the encore live after this.
ごめんね、これ3人用なんだ。
Sorry, this is for three people.
いやいやいや、こんなに席あったのに、3人用だったの、これ？
Wait, wait, wait, there were so many seats, but it was for three people?
そうなの。
Yes.
4人の乗ると止まっちゃう。
If four people ride, it stops.
止まっちゃう？重さで？莉々華の体重のせいで？
It stops? From weight? Because of Ririka's weight?
まあ、なんか言ってますけれどもね。
Well, they're saying that, but...
この後、莉々華はメインディッシュのアンコールライブがあります！
...after this, Ririka has the main dish, the encore live!
おお、頑張れ！
Oh, do your best!
アンコールライブでは、ホロライブのあの曲や、あの曲を歌っちゃう！
For the encore live, I'll be singing that Hololive song, and that song!
と思っているので、楽しんでもらえると嬉しいです！
...so I hope you'll enjoy it!
じゃあみんな、今日来てくれて本当にありがとね！
Alright everyone, thank you so much for coming today!
この後もゆっくり楽しんでね！バイバイ！
Keep enjoying the rest of the show! Bye-bye!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
大スキな秘書みならい一人一人へ
苦手だった歌やダンスをがんばりたい！って
思えるようになったのはみんなのおかげだよ。
To each and every one of my beloved apprentice secretaries:
It's thanks to all of you that I wanted to do my best
at singing and dancing, which I used to be bad at.
これからもずっとそばで応援してくれる？
変わらない毎日と 新しいチャレンジを一緒に...
Will you continue to support me by my side?
Together through our unchanging daily lives and new challenges...
ホロライブに入れてよかった！！！
ririka
I'm so glad I joined Hololive!!!
- ririka